The Symphony Upon the Ship
The fireworks will start soon.
Please enjoy the glamorous show that
will spread across the night sky.
May this be a lovely memory for
the last night of the cruise.
For now, let's head to the third cargo room,
where the rubber boats are stored.
That's where the director is.
We'll lower the boat from the emergency
exit at the front of the second deck.
Then, we'll have the rendezvous
ship retrieve you.
If possible, we should do
this during the fireworks.
What should we do with our extra time?
Watch the fireworks?
No way. We're heading to the casino.
I'm gonna win big so I can kiss my
job as a civil servant goodbye!
The director's gonna yell at you.
L-Let's keep our guard up as we proceed.
Y-Yeah...
Blue Lace No. 89 and Mermaid...
They're both famous perfumes.
But the combination of those two scents,
as well as the woman without a scent...
One man, two women, and a baby.
I've found you.
Anya loves fireworks!
Do you?
Papa!
I wanna look over there, too!
There are too many people.
I can't see the sky.
I wonder if we'll find Mama.
It probably won't be that easy.
I'm so excited.
Is it starting soon?
I'm going to propose to my
girlfriend at the finale.
There are so many excited voices that
I can't tell if Mama is even around.
So excited.
I wonder when I should tell her that she's
more beautiful than the fireworks.
So excited.
I'm going to have to
concentwate to find her.
Those people could be assassins.
To think their reach extends
all the way down here...
Let's go around them.
This way, too.
All the routes to the
bow have been blocked.
Of course, I could defeat
them and make my way through,
but they might call for backup.
They might also figure
out where we're going.
Let's head back up to the deck for now.
Is everything okay?
The director gave me a key
that opens the crew corridors.
Let's sneak out via the roof or other
paths that other people wouldn't use.
I don't sense anyone here.
Everyone's probably busy with
the event, so we should be fine,
but let's do our best not to make any noise.
Shh.
O-Okay...
Let's go.
Th-That startled me.
It's all right. Look at
the pretty fireworks.
Let's use this noise as a
distraction to get away.
Up here!
Hup!
Wow.
Let's hurry over there.
I see two with black hair.
Is it the one holding the brat?
Yeah. If possible, take the baby
out while you're at it, too.
Roger.
She dodged it?!
Oh, dear... He dodged it.
Are you hurt?
Miss!
I-I'm okay... I think.
I didn't feel their presence.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
They're all very strong.
We won't be able to escape.
I won't miss this time. I'll kill you first.
Honestly...
I was wondering where you
were wasting time.
Director!
Tch. So she has friends.
You two, run!
Take shelter under that hatch.
You're not getting away!
Miss, hurry!
Too bad.
Someone in my blind spot?!
Zeb!
That hurt! Even with the
bulletproof vest on, that hurt!
Don't push yourself so hard!
Nice, Mister Husband!
Hi-yah!
I can breathe easier knowing
that hatch won't open easily.
You think that did you any good?
I'll blow you all to smithereens!
Pardon.
Tch.
Don't poke your body out!
Not good. The deck is getting quite dirty.
I'll need to properly sanitize it
and get rid of all the evidence.
You're mi—
Could you try to finish them
off without making such a mess?
It's becoming a pain to clean up after you.
Director! When did you...
I'm terribly sorry. I haven't
had much time to consider that.
Well, I suppose that can't be helped.
They all seem to be proficient killers,
including a number of outsiders
with unique fighting styles
we haven't seen before.
But...
They are no match for us, the Garden.
Having them all gathered in one
spot will work in our favor.
Let us finish them all off.
Wow! Now it's a red one!
I don't know how you can be equally excited
by every single one that goes up.
Bravo!
Oh, crap, Vides! I won!
This poison is enough to take a bear down!
Goodness! You're so rude.
Esmerelda, the master of wire—
I'm the king of chak—
All right! The fireworks show
is reaching its climax!
That hurt!
Just, "That hurt"?
And the party is finished!
I jammed my finger...
Well, damn.
You ended up killing all
of them, you awful woman.
Huh? Yes, I did kill them.
It was only natural. I'm terribly sorry.
Those who point their blade at another
cannot complain when they
have one pointed at them.
That includes myself.
You're so earnest. Well, no matter.
This just means I get a
bigger cut of the money.
This might be a bit late to ask,
but would you consider just
peacefully going home?
I'd rather not spill any
more unnecessary blood.
Who do you think you are?
That's not going to happen.
We've already received a down payment,
and it's not like we can go
home when we're on a boat.
I'm also pretty sure that old guy
over there isn't gonna let us leave.
You shouldn't glare at them
like that, Director!
This lot considers war just
another way to get paid.
If we let them go, they will
harm our country somehow.
You're old-fashioned, Mister Soldier.
You should learn a thing or two
from the West. Money is power.
Everyone's happy if we're all rich, right?
To be a businessman,
you truly lack foresight.
You can regret playing with fire
while the sharks are eating you.
Nah... You're the ones who're
gonna end up as shark bait.
Director!
My grip strength...
It's over.
Don't struggle. You're just
drawing out your suffering.
He's on a different level than the others.
My legs are heavy again.
In the event of your death or a wound too
severe for a cover story to account for,
I will tell Forger that you
have been transferred.
If I disappeared without saying a word...
What an awful woman I would be.
They'll be suspicious if I come home
with a new hairstyle, too!
What?! You got a haircut
while entertaining guests?!
Er, well, this was just how I dealt
with them turning down our offer.
No, now's not the time to
be worrying about that!
At this rate, I'm going to be sliced in two!
Little girl, if you're afraid
of dying, then retreat now.
I-I cannot!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Olka or the others!
Sucks being at the bottom
of the ladder, huh?
If you'll yield, I don't mind giving you a cut.
I'd rather not get hurt anyway.
I don't want a cut! Don't be ridiculous!
I'm not being ridiculous, though.
This is a very serious business discussion.
You're just like us. You put
food on your table by killing.
Don't compare me to you! I'm—
I'm doing this to support my family... wait.
I guess I am also doing this for money.
But... no, I make enough to survive now...
I'm hunting down bad guys for my country!
For my country?
Have I always been so righteous?
What am I doing this for?
Oh, no—
Oh, dear. He might actually
kill me. What should I do?
Now I won't be able to get Loid's
shirts from the cleaners.
I also won't be able to return
Miss Anya's library books.
Wait, what am I even saying?
Why is this gentleman pointing
a giant sword at me?
My head hurts...
I think I'm a bit tired.
Sis! Sis!
Oh... I'm starting to see visions of Yuri.
Yahoo-hoo! Sis! I received an unofficial
offer from foreign affairs!
Aw, Yuri... you've grown up so much.
I bought this with my first paycheck!
You can survive on your own without my help.
Oh, my!
I don't need to kill for a living anymore.
Yes...
Let's end this.
After all, if I die, I won't be able
to go to the cleaners or the library.
It's over. Finish off Olka and the others.
Got it.
No...
You little...
Olka?
Olka. Why was I acting
as her bodyguard again?
I just want to live a quiet, peaceful life.
That's right.
The reason I started this job...
and continued this job...
Life had gotten so hectic that
I had completely forgotten.
Was it for money? For my country?
It was, but it wasn't.
I just...
I just wanted to protect his simple life.
There are many unreasonable
sacrifices in the world.
To make sure I don't add to them...
To reduce that number by even one...
I need to thoroughly cleanse this world.
Things are not going to change.
No... Now more than ever...
I don't need peace.
I don't care if there is blood on these hands.
Even if I live a life in which I'm
bound to be killed sooner or later...
Even if I have to leave the Forgers...
Be it for someone else,
or for a specific reason,
having to endure a merciless job...
That's something to be very proud of.
I'm sure Loid will acknowledge me.
He'll forgive me.
I will not give up...
this fight!
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Sis's Herb Tea
He went around the back.
We're going to surround him, Yuri!
Roger!
What's wrong, Yuri?!
Did the suspect get you?!
Sir... it appears that...
I caught a cold.
Out of nowhere?!
It's rare for you to get sick.
When I...
When I think about my sister not
being around, my cells grow weak.
Oh, right. She's on a business
trip right now, isn't she?
On that cruise.
I'm sorry I let the suspect get away.
Just get some rest.
I'm going to the drug store.
Oh, wait...
Could you also get me some herbal tea?
The one with the bear on it.
Fine.
Whenever I get a cold,
I remember when I was little...
Oh, no! You have a fever, Yuri.
What should I do? What should I do?
Calm down, Sis.
I'll be fine if I get some rest.
First things first! You need to stay warm!
I'll put every piece of cloth we have over you!
Heavy! That's too heavy, Sis!
Apparently, in the far east, they wrap
green onions around their necks!
I give! Sis, I give up!
Nothin' beats herbal tea
with some honey for colds.
Try putting elderflower or sage in it.
Thanks, Mrs. Nabor!
I'm heading to the mountains now!
I'm home, Yuri!
I picked up a bunch of things
that are really good for you!
Sis?! What in the world happened to you?!
Oh, I just accidentally made
some bees mad, tee-hee.
Oh, and I fought a boar.
Let's make you some hotpot!
And I'll make you some
herbal tea right away!
This isn't good... Me having a cold
puts my sister's life in danger!
I need to grow up big and strong.
Hurry up and get better, Yuri!
Hey, Sis.
Hm?
I'm really glad I'm your little brother.
Goodness, don't talk like you're going to die.
I'm fine.
I'm glad I have you by my side, too.
Stay happy and healthy forever, okay?
Sis...
I need to make this world gentler...
someday, for my gentle sister...
Here. Drink this and get better soon.
I will, thanks.
This sure warms you right up!
Oh, thank goodness.
There's so much going on
in my body right now
that I'm not worried about my
cold symptoms at all anymore!
Oh, thank goodness!
You all right? You wouldn't
stop moaning in your sleep.
I bought the stuff you asked for.
Thank you very much.
This stuff is famous for tasting awful.
Mr. Bear
Cold and Flu
It works the best for me.
It also tastes the most similar to
what my sister would make for me.
All right! All better!
Let's go catch that suspect!
I'm going to purify the world
before my sister gets back!
Stay in bed!
The Hand That Connects to the Future